mathnasium.ca 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Mathnasium

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 23, 2015

Mathnasium, LLC, a California limited liability company (“ **Mathnasium** ”, “ **we** ” or “ **us** ”) has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies and practices with respect to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of personal information which you may provide while using, or that we may obtain from your use of, www.mathnasium.ca and/or http://mathnasiumfranchise.com/ (individually and collectively, the “ **Website** ”).

**Your Consent**

By using the Website, you signify your consent to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy or if you do not think this Privacy Policy provides you enough protection, you may not use or visit the Website.

**Non-Identifiable Information Automatically Collected**

Like many other websites, the Website may automatically collect certain non-identifiable information regarding Website visitors, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, the IP address of your Internet Service Provider, the date and time you access the Website, the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to the Website, the operating system you are using, the sections of the Website you visit, the Website pages read and images viewed, and the materials you post to or download from the Website. This non-identifiable information is used for Website and system administration purposes and to improve the Website. Your non-identifiable information may be disclosed to others and permanently archived for future use.

**Cookies**

The Website uses “cookies”, a technology that installs information on a website visitor’s computer to permit the website to recognize future visits using that computer. The cookies used by the Website do not contain any personal information regarding Website visitors, and do not retrieve any information from visitors’ personal computers (other than IP address and other similar information retrieved or retained in order to facilitate your use of the Website). Cookies are used only to enhance the visitor’s experience on the Website, and to collect anonymous traffic data to enable us to provide a better web experience for the viewing public in general. You may choose to decline cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may affect your use of the Website and your ability to access certain features of the Website.

**Tracking Information**

Mathnasium may use non-personal information to create aggregate tracking information reports regarding Website user demographics and Website traffic patterns. This information helps us to customize the Website to better meet your online needs, improve our services and conduct research. None of the tracking information in the reports can be connected to the identities or other personal information of individual website visitors or other individuals. If Mathnasium links tracking information with personal information, any of the linked information will be treated as personal information and will be used and disclosed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and in accordance with the law.

**Your Personal Information** \- During your use of the Website, you may be asked to voluntarily provide certain personal information (such as, should you decide to complete the “Contact Mathnasium” form, your name, email address, postal address, and telephone number).  Mathnasium may collect and use your personal information to present the Website, its content and features to you, to contact and correspond with you, to respond to your inquiries and provide you with information that you request from us, to notify you about upcoming events, products and/or services offered or provided by us, our affiliates and/or our franchisees that may be of interest to you, and as otherwise permitted by law.

**Sharing of Personal Information** – Mathnasium may disclose personal information that we collect through the Website to affiliates, franchisees and service providers for the purposes identified above. Only Mathnasium employees, affiliates, franchisees and service providers with proper authorization will have access to your personal information, and only to the extent necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  Our service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes.

Mathnasium franchises are independently owned and operated. As a result, Mathnasium cannot guarantee that a franchisee will comply with this Privacy Policy; however, we will make an effort to require that franchisees comply.

**Disclosure of Your Personal Information** – Mathnasium may disclose your personal information to a government institution that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information or where Mathnasium has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful in the investigation of unlawful activity, or to comply with a subpoena or warrant or an order made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction to compel the production of information, or to comply with court rules regarding the production of records and information, or to protect Mathnasium's rights and property or as otherwise required or permitted by law. If Mathnasium is involved in a merger, sale or other reorganization involving all or part of Mathnasium, Mathnasium may disclose your personal information to the purchaser or resulting organization.

**Storing and Securing Your Personal Information** \- Mathnasium may store and process your personal information collected through the Website in our offices at 5120 W. Goldleaf Circle, Suite 300, Los Angeles, CA 90056 and/or the offices of our affiliates, franchisees and/or service providers located in Canada, the United States or other jurisdictions.  As such, personal information may be subject to foreign laws and may be accessible by foreign governments, courts, law enforcement and regulatory agencies. By using the Website, you consent to such storage and processing in and outside of the jurisdiction in which you reside.  To help protect the confidentiality of your personal information, Mathnasium uses reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  Nevertheless, due to the nature of the Internet and Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and Mathnasium cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

**Accessing Your Personal Information** \- You may request access to your personal information and information about Mathnasium's collection, use and disclosure of that information by contacting our Privacy Officer at: tracy.cramer@mathnasium.com.  Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information, and will be entitled to challenge the accuracy and completeness of such information and to have it amended as appropriate. You can help Mathnasium maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any changes to your personal information.

**About Children**

Mathnasium does not knowingly collect, solicit or maintain information provided by children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

**Links to Other Websites**

This Website may contain links or references to other websites or Internet resources. Please be aware that Mathnasium does not control such other websites and that, in any case, this Privacy Policy does not apply to such other websites.  When you click on one of those links you are contacting another website or Internet resource that may collect information about you voluntarily or through cookies or other technologies. Mathnasium has no responsibility or liability for those other websites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information.

**How to Contact Us**

Mathnasium welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Policy.  If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of Mathnasium, its affiliates and/or its franchisees and service providers in respect of the collection, storage, use and disclosure of personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer at tracy.cramer@mathnasium.com.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be changed by Mathnasium from time to time in Mathnasium’s sole discretion and without any prior notice or liability to you or any other person. The collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by Mathnasium will be governed by the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at that time.  If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this Website.  Your continued use of the Website will signify that you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the changed Privacy Policy. Accordingly, when you use the Website, you should check the date of this Privacy Policy and review any changes since the last version. You should also bookmark this page and periodically review this Privacy Policy to ensure that you are familiar with the most current version.

MTL01: 3281208: v2
